FARAZ KORASANI

Sydney NSW 2067 0451 287 563 Faraz.korasani@gmail.com

A developer and designer based in Sydney, Australia, with 19+ years of teaching experience in the ESL and EFL industries, I am ready to start a new journey.



Portfolio link: https://farazkorasani.github.io/portfolio/

Skills

- Web Development HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Vue, C#, PHP, MySQL, Git/GitHub
- Multimedia Design Adobe Photoshop, FlexClip, Figma, P5.js
- Game Development Unreal Engine 5
- ESL EAP, Exam Prep, Business English, Academic/Creative Writing

Qualifications

- CELTA (pass B) International House Sydney, Sydney, Australia
- Bachelor's Degree in English Literature Allameh Tabataba'i University, Tehran, Iran
- Associate Degree in English Literature Allameh Tabataba'i University, Tehran, Iran
- Academic IELTS 8.5
- General IELTS 8.5
- iBT (TOEFL) 118
- GRE 320 (Full Verbal Score)

Publications

• Faraz Korasani. "Q Skills for Success Level 2 Book Review". *English Australia Journal* 37.1 (2021): 103-107.

Professional Experience

ILSC Sydney- Sydney, Australia

English Teacher, Mar 2019 - Apr 2024

IELTS Preparation Courses (Online and On-Campus)

- English for Academic Purposes Courses (Online and On-Campus)
- General English Courses (Online and On-Campus)

International House Sydney- Sydney, Australia

English Teacher, Jan 2019 – Feb 2019

• General English courses; English File 3rd Edition

Tehran Institute of Technology – Tehran, Iran

English teacher, Aug 2011 – Aug 2018

- Exam prep courses; general & academic IELTS, PBT, and iBT
- GRE preparation courses
- General English courses; New Interchange, Passages, and English Result
- Business English courses
- Dogme conversation/free discussion courses
- Accent Reduction Courses

Aryanpour Novin Language Institute – Tehran, Iran

English Teacher, Jan 2007 - Jun 2011

- General English courses; New Interchange, Passages, and American English File
- Dogme conversation/free discussion courses

Freelance – Tehran, Iran

English teacher, Dec 2005 – Aug 2018

- Exam prep courses; general & academic IELTS, PBT, and iBT
- General English courses; Streamline, Touchstone & Viewpoint
- Conversation courses; Function & American Street Talk (vol. 1 & 3)

References

- Yulianto Lukito; Cambridge CELTA Senior Trainer at IH and ILSC Australia;
 YLukito@ihsydney.com.au
- Aaron Clark; Head Teacher at ILSC Australia; Aaron.Clark@ilsc.com.au